Inbal Schwimmer Shafir

052-3807159 || inbalschwimmer@gmail.com

Experienced manual and automation tester with over 10 years of experience, experienced in testing for multiple platforms such as mobile applications, web and desktop. Recently wrote automation tests. As for today I'm looking for manual QA Engineer and Automation Engineer position.

Work Experience

2020 - 2024 - Rakuten Viber

2022 - 2024 - Automation Tests Engineer

- Part of an Automation team
- Web system for writing automation tests based on Selenium, Appium.
- Maintaining of existing scenarios, Creating new elements.
- Employees training on writing automation tests.
- Worked with Intellij, Java, Xcode.

2020 - 2022 - Manual QA Engineer as part of the Server Tests team

- Part of OA Server team.
- Testing AWS using Kibana, S3.
- API testing using Postman.
- Wrote STD in TestRail and bug documentation in Jira.

2016 - 2020 Nice Actimize - Automation QA Test Engineer

- Tested products for traffic security in the banking industry.
- Cloud SaaS solutions worked closely with development teams, writing microservices and integration tests using Python, EC2, DynamoDB, API Gat4eaway, S3, Jenkins, and GitLab.
- On-prem products performed server tests using SoapUI, worked with MsSQL, Oracle.
- Wrote STD documentation in QC and RTC.
- Experience working on Agile-Scrum methodology.

2013 - 2015 - Paymax - QA Test Engineer

- Manual tests for lottery forms for mobile and tablets.
- Sanity tests, Regression, and UX UI tests on iOS and Android platforms.

2012 - 2013 - 888 Holdings - QA Test Engineer

• Manual tests for mobile and tablet devices.

- SoapUl, SQLserver, MTM, Fiddler, Xpolog.
- Wrote STR, STD, STP documentation

Previous roles: QA Engineer, Data Manager, Tech Support

Knowledge and Skills

Programming Languages: C, Java, Python

• Testing Tools: Selenium, Appium, SoapUI

Database: SQL

• OS: Windows, Linux, Mac, iOS, and Android

Cloud Platform: AWS

• Version Control: Git, GitLab

• Documentation: Jira, QC, MTM, Spira

Education

B.A in Management, the Open University

Software Testing Course - C, Python, Java, NESS College

<u>Languages</u>

Hebrew – Mother tongue; English – High level